Hi, my name is **Henya Adler**

I'm looking for UX/UI Designer

Check My Portfolio

Contact me

+972 58 778 2 776 henyadesign@gmail.com www.henya.me LinkedIn Facebook

Skills

After Effects Photoshop Premier Pro

Illustrator

XD

InDesign

Figma

Wordpress

HTML

CSS

Languages

Hebrew

English

Ukrainian

Russian

Spanish

Projects

Books exchange app

Conference website

Website for trading

Italian restaurant app

I'm a highly skilled and versatile designer with experience in designing, animating, branding, prototyping, and basic coding. I specialize in creating user-friendly designs and am committed to improving the user experience through user research, simplification, and visual design. Overall, my passion for design and my commitment to improving the user experience drive me to continuously improve my skills and expertise.

Experience

Marketing Designer

Agilite

2023 - present

- Designed ads, banners, newsletters.
- Created animations
- Creating and Editing Technical documents.

Marketing Designer

Castro-Hoodies

2022 - 2023

Replacement for maternity leave

- Designed ads, banners, newsletters.
- Designed brand identity.
- Created animations and videos.
- Redesigning from scratch e-commerce websites.

UX/UI Designer

Rom Marketing

2020 - 2022

- Designed wireframes and UI.
- Designed brand identity.
- Created animations and videos.

Graphic Designer

Nail Pharm

2017 - 2019

- Developed and perfected skills in marketing, branding, and other areas.
- Delivered advertising materials for social media, banners, print and packaging materials.

Graphic Design - Freelance

Henya Design

2017 - 2022

- Created brand identity.
- Created print materials.
- Created Wordpress websites using Elementor/ Gutenberg.

Education

UX/UI Design

Netcraft academy

2020 - 2021

Graphic Design

Shenkar Handesaim

2016 - 2017

Advertising & Brand Communication (B.A.)

MEGI Institute

2009 - 2014